[
	{
		"question": "Who wrote about a 'Fifth Emperor'?",
		"answers": ["Morgans"]
	},
	{
		"question": "Luffy father name?",
		"answers": ["dragon"]
	},
	{
		"question": "Who of the eleven Supernovas ate a Zoan Devil Fruit?",
		"answers": ["X Drake","Drake"]
	},
	{
		"question": "Luffy brother name?",
		"answers": ["ace"]
	},
	{
		"question": "Who was the first woman to kiss Luffy?",
		"answers": ["reiju","sanji sister"]
	},
	{
		"question": "Who was the first Admiral to be shown in the series?",
		"answers": ["Aokiji"]
	},
	{
		"question": "Where was Gol D. Roger born?",
		"answers": ["East Blue"]
	},
	{
		"question": "Which 'One Piece' character is the captain of the of the Straw Hat Pirates, who wears a straw hat himself?",
		"answers": ["Luffy"]
	},
	{
		"question": "Who promised that they would never lose another fight until they defeated a certain someone??",
		"answers": ["zoro"]
	},
	{
		"question": " What reason does Sanji give for not fighting Kalifa?",
		"answers": ["woman"]
	},
	{
		"question": "True or false; Mr. 3 took out Brogy the giant with explosives?",
		"answers": ["false"]
	},
	{
		"question": " How many CP9 agents went under cover at the Galley-La Company?",
		"answers": ["3","three"]
	},
	{
		"question": "True or false; Lola's zombie was a warthog?",
		"answers": ["true"]
	},
	{
		"question": "What was the name of Brook's former crew?",
		"answers": ["The Rumbar Pirates"]
	},
	{
		"question": "What are the names of Senor Pink's deceased wife?",
		"answers": ["Russian"]
	},
	{
		"question": "What happens when if someone eats a second Devil Fruit?",
		"answers": ["die","dead"]
	},
	{
		"question": "How many 'hells' exist in Impel Down?",
		"answers": ["6","six"]
	},
	{
		"question": " What does the name 'Kuja' mean?",
		"answers": ["Nine snakes","Nine snake"]
	},
	{
		"question": "How many crewmates did Luffy say he wanted at the beginning of the series?",
		"answers": ["10","ten"]
	},
	{
		"question": "How did Luffy get the scar under his eye?",
		"answers": ["Himself"]
	},
	{
		"question": "Who was the first member of the SH crew to try and recruit a new member besides Luffy?",
		"answers": ["nami"]
	},
	{
		"question": "Who was the first villain to defeat Luffy? ",
		"answers": ["Crocodile"]
	},
	{
		"question": "What made Crocodile join Luffy's 'Rescue Ace Crew'?",
		"answers": ["Ivankov"]
	},
	{
		"question": "Akainu lost in his battle against Kuzan for Fleet Admiral. State true or false?",
		"answers": ["False"]
	},
	{
		"question": "Who said the Zoro should cut diamond next?",
		"answers": ["Daz Bones"]
	},
	{
		"question": "Who was the first recruit of the SH crew?",
		"answers": ["zoro"]
	},
	{
		"question": "What does Pagaya call the component which is in both sea stones and the clouds of Sky Island?",
		"answers": ["Pyrbloin"]
	},
	{
		"question": "What is the money in Skypia called? hint:Ex___",
		"answers": ["Extol"]
	},
	{
		"question": "What Devil Fruit type is Luffy?",
		"answers": ["Mythical Zoan","zoan"]
	},
	{
		"question": "What is Luffy Devil Fruit real name?",
		"answers": ["Gum Gum Fruit","Hito Hito No Mi"]
	},
	{
		"question": "How many rings are behind Bellamy's figurehead?",
		"answers": ["4","four"]
	},
	{
		"question": "Say any one of Chopper's forms?",
		"answers": ["Arm Point","Brain Point","Guard Point","Heavy Point","Horn Point","Jumping Point","Monster Point"]
	},
	{
		"question": "Who gave Shanks the scar on his eye?",
		"answers": ["Marshall D. Teach","Blackbeard","teach"]
	},
	{
		"question": "How long did Portgas D. Rouge's pregnancy last?",
		"answers": ["Twenty months","20 month","Twenty month"]
	}
]